Guide to the Arthur Lee Loeb papers M1590
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives
- Series 8: Academic Juvenalia
  - Notebook: "An Interionic attraction theory..." (Box 106, Folder 11)
- Series 9. Born-Digital Materials
  Access to Series 9:
  Born-digital materials are CLOSED until data is fully accessioned and processed.
  - Obsolete computer media: 56 5.25" floppies, 51 3.5" floppies, 4 CD-RW, 4 data cartridges, 34 zip disks. CLOSED UNTIL PROCESSED.
- Series 10. Oversize Materials
  Series 10, Oversize Materials, consist of paste-ups for Loeb's books and articles as well as photographs of his models.
  - Paste-ups for articles by Arthur Loeb (Flat-box 107, Folders 1-6)
  - Photographs of geometric models (Flat-box 108, Folder 104)